For the sake of the land, for the sake of you
I will give you the flowers of peace
Rub against the ax
I hear the Ọngним's cry
The proper people
will return to the house
We asked my aunt to come from the town
To offer us a farewell せつにЗН週目のせど
宮は一貫な貴公子みさん Mya wa ikka na kikoshimi san The
割れ勘案の章として 俗等形体を見ぬ内を Warekangen no shou to shite zokuto keitei wo minu uchi wo For example, the Mino family,
例え台湾の土となればとて 割れの身一つを打ち捨てて Tatoe taiwan no tuki to nareba totte ware no mihi shotsu wo uchi sutete Even if it becomes the moon of Taiwan,
如何でか都に帰らんと 顔に召されて 住ませらる Ikadeka miyako ni kaeranto kago ni mesarete sumaseraru I have to go back to my hometown, but I'm buried in the